Chief, excuse me.
Someone's looking for you downstairs.
Didn't you say you would give me a tour
of your office when you had time?
- [JORDAN] It's kinda weird, right?
- Abi.
"I'd like to thank someone
very special to me."
"My younger brother, Oliver."
Where are your parents?
They're dead.
They're long gone.
[JORDAN] I spoke with the taxi driver
already. He agreed to meet.
[BILLY] Maybe we need to let
the authorities handle this.
[JORDAN]
You know that won't achieve anything.
- Caloy! Let him go.
- And your family--
You still haven't learned your lesson?
Huh? [GRUNTS]
- [CALOY SHOUTS]
- [BLOWS LAND]
Is that all you got?
[GRUNTS]
- [GRUNTS, LAUGHS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
[EXCLAIMS]
[SPITS]
That's what you get
for not minding your business!
- [SLAP LANDS]
- [WHIMPERS]
- [SOBS] I'm sorry.
- Stay out of it, kid.
- This is between your mom and me!
- Stop it!
- Huh?!
- Enough! Leave him alone!
- Back off!
- [BODY THUDS]
Enough, Daddy! Please!
- Dad! [SOBS]
- Knock it off!
- Stay out of it!
- Hey!
- [WHIMPERS]
- Stop it!
You're hurting him!
Let him go!
[SLAPS]
- Enough!
- [JADE SHOUTS]
[CALOY GRUNTS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [JORDAN GRUNTS]
[SHOUTS]
[KICKS, BLOWS LANDING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [CALOY GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[KICKS, BLOW LAND]
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
Oh my goodness!
- [PEOPLE MURMURING] Poor guy.
- [GRUNTS LOUDLY]
Who's your boss?
Who was that woman?
- What woman?
- Tell me!
I don't know what you're talking about!
I swear!
- Tell me!
- I have nothing to tell you!
Tell me, Caloy.
I have nothing to say!
Who was that woman?!
Help me!
Please, help me!
- Help! Please! Please, help me!
- Hey!
[JORDAN] Let me go!
He's the criminal! Not me!
- Please, help me.
- Caloy!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Auntie Pres.
- Billy.
- Oliver.
- Billy…
- Are you okay?
- Billy.
- What happened?
I'm fine. I just got into a fight.
I told him that
he should've told his teacher.
There was no teacher around then.
Oliver, what happened?
Who started it?
He did.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
He punched me first!
That's not true!
This kid is such a liar!
- Excuse me. Please don't call him a liar.
- Why shouldn't we?
You better not expect our son
to apologize for what happened!
Look at the poor thing!
Where are his parents?!
[PRECIOUS] I am his legal guardian.
Auntie Precious and I
are Oliver's legal guardians.
And my brother is not a liar.
We told him to stay away from trouble
as much as possible.
But we also taught him
to fight back when necessary.
Ah, so you're the one
who taught this kid to be violent?
Again, as long as it's self-defense.
So you're perfectly fine
with Oliver punching our son?
- Yes!
- Of course not.
Huh?
No wonder your brother is a delinquent.
You're tolerating his bad behavior!
What a shameless family!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BILLY GRUNTS]
- [GASPING]
You should be ashamed!
A kid defending himself
doesn't make him a delinquent.
Dr. Ronquillo,
can we call this kid's real parents?
I don't want to talk to these people!
They're both gone,
so you'll have to deal with us.
Folks, let's all act like adults.
Someone will be joining us
to tell us what really happened.
[DOOR OPENS]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
I asked them to join us so we can
hear Suzie's side of the story.
Suzie, who really started the fight?
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you again.
Sir Edgar, thank you.
Thank you for coming.
We just did the right thing
by telling the truth.
Thank you for protecting our baby.
Thank you for the cupcakes as well.
Biboy is really a bully.
He won't stop.
You don't have to worry about him, Suzie.
Aren't you scared of him?
Him and his entire group?
Nope. I'm not backing down from them.
I'm brave like my big sister.
- Mm…
- Very good.
You two are like peas in a pod.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BUSY TONE]
- [UTENSILS CLINK]
- Fork here.
How do you feel? Does it still hurt?
No, Billy. It's just a small bruise.
- No, Oliver.
- Put some ice on it.
That small bruise of yours
will take time to heal.
But it'll still heal, right?
[MOUTHS] No!
I'm sorry, Auntie.
I'm sorry too, Billy.
I know you guys are busy.
I'm sorry for being a burden.
What? Don't say that, Oliver.
You're never going to be a burden.
- You're our baby boy!
- No!
Tsk, I'm not a baby anymore!
Stop calling me that!
Okay, fine. You're not
our baby boy anymore,
but you will never be a burden to us.
Auntie Pres and I
will always have your back.
Me too, Billy.
That's why I'm bulking up. See?
- Look at those biceps!
- Cut that out.
You already punched someone.
Violence is never the answer, Oliver!
I know, Auntie.
But all I'm saying is,
if anyone hurts Billy?
- I'll knock them out.
- Unbelievable.
- You don't listen, do you?
- Just like Billy.
Don't blame me.
- Put some ice on that.
- Listen to me, Billy.
Stop tolerating Oliver's behavior.
- It is wrong and unacceptable.
- [BILLY] But--
- Hear me out--
- No, no, no.
No buts, no hear-me-outs. None of that.
Violence is wrong.
It doesn't matter who started it,
the bottom line is, no fighting.
[OLIVER] Uh-oh.
Okay, Auntie Pres. Calm down.
- Chill out, Auntie.
- I'm worried about you two.
- Yes, we know.
- Let's hug it out.
- Come on!
- Chill, okay?
- Chill? Whatever! Let's eat.
- [BOTH EXCLAIM]
No violence, remember?
- That's wrong.
- Yes.
- No to violence.
- Oh, really?
- [EXCLAIMS] Get him!
- [OLIVER SHOUTS]
- I am not a criminal.
- Nope.
He is.
Check his record.
[OFFICER] We already have.
According to his record,
it was an act of self-defense.
Bull!
Chief, ask the people who were there.
They'll tell you the truth.
They witnessed it!
You think you're the victim here?
A lot of people can testify!
You were caught on video
trying to stab me!
I wasn't looking for trouble!
- You attacked me!
- That's not true.
Don't believe him! He's a hacker!
- Chief…
- He's an online troll!
- What?!
- And a big fat liar!
- Wait…
- Look, I'm injured!
Sir, he's been harassing me and my friend.
We had him arrested before.
- You should go to jail!
- [ROBBIE] What the hell?
- What did you say?!
- Hey!
- See?! See?!
- Stop it!
Cuff him!
- Arrest him!
- This is going online!
- Stop that!
- Don't record this!
[OFFICER] Enough.
Lock him up already, chief!
Boss, are you all right? Boss?
- [JORDAN GRUNTS]
- Boss.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAMERAS CLICKING]
ARM DAY FOR ME! NO SWEAT, NO GAIN.
Oh…
- Someone's happy.
- Hmm?
Is that why you're smiling, Auntie Pres?
- Because of Brandon?
- Mm.
He's not just charitable.
He's also athletic.
- Mm-hmm.
- Watch out, Auntie Pres.
He must throw a mean punch too.
Boxing's just one of his hobbies.
You're defending him!
No, I'm just reading
what's listed on his profile.
- Don't be silly.
- Are you two talking?
Huh? It's too soon.
Okay, Auntie Pres.
If you're scared or unsure,
use the LoveSpeak feature.
Mm.
Ask if anyone knows Brandon.
Their feedback can help you
get to know him.
Maybe next time. I'm busy.
With what?
With the sanctuary,
with Oliver, and even here at home.
And you too.
We're okay.
We're fine!
Your baby boy is all grown up
and won't even let you hug him.
Hmph!
It's your turn.
Huh?
Why are we talking about me now?
Why don't you
put yourself first this time?
I'm trying!
Is it my fault no one passes
my very long checklist?
Passing that checklist of yours
is an impossible task.
Besides, your life
revolves around home and work.
It's always home, work, home, work.
How will you meet someone
who ticks all the boxes?
Listen, Billy.
You've been working hard
since you were a kid.
- Mm-hmm.
- Am I right?
Even after I told you countless times,
"Billy, I got this."
You refuse to slow down.
You'd put Biboy's father to shame
if he found out all the sacrifices
you made for Oliver.
For all of us.
He was asking for
Oliver's parents, wasn't he?
Well, he should know that you are
basically Oliver's mom and dad.
You sacrificed your childhood
to raise him.
You didn't get to have fun.
- Huh?
- [PHONE RINGING]
And who says I'm not having fun?
Mm-hmm.
Hello?
Yes, Rain?
Huh?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What happened?
- Jordan!
- Ma'am.
- Boss, I'm his friend.
- Go ahead.
What the hell?
I told you guys not to tell her!
I was going to fix this myself.
Rain called her.
- Wow, traitor.
- You did.
How's Oliver?
Oliver is fine, but you're not.
- You are so stubborn!
- Ow!
I just wanted to talk to the taxi driver.
I know the whole story.
Okay.
But on the bright side…
Jordan, stop.
No, really. Look,
Caloy filed a case against me.
I'll file a case against him too.
So that means…
A legal battle.
Yes.
We'll be able to dig up info on Caloy.
Maybe we'll find clues or evidence
that'll lead us to his employer.
And how will you do that
if you're in jail?
Everything will be okay.
Boss.
Physical assault, grave threats,
and they added possession
of a deadly weapon.
That's a hefty bail.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I can handle it.
But the problem is,
we just paid the rent for the bar.
And didn't you just cash out
for your grandfather's…
Rain! Shh!
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Look, dude…
I'm sorry.
You know, honestly,
I really want to smack you right now.
But I'll save that for when you get out.
Let's figure something out.
Look, I can handle the bail.
I don't think it's that much.
Yeah, boss, but…
we're still waiting for the person
who has to sign your release.
So I think
stay.
Stay.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Guys, go home.
I'll be okay.
- Ma'am, thank you.
- Thank you!
You're welcome!
There's more if you want a second round.
Go ahead. Eat up.
Boss, where did you live
before you went to prison?
Hmm. You've gone viral now.
LOVELIST'S JORDAN VALENTIN
INVOLVED IN ASSAULT.
I don't want to see it.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I just want to know the truth.
But not like this.
Not this way.
What happened to you?
Why did you suddenly snap?
You're not like this.
[JADE SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
[JADE CHOKING]
[THUDS]
[DINO GRUNTS]
[JUDE] Get out before I kill you!
Get out!
[GROANING]
[DINO PANTING]
I'm not afraid of you, old man.
What about the police? Still not afraid?
I know all the dirty things you've done.
I'll have you arrested for dealing drugs
and for abusing my daughter and grandson.
[YOUNG JORDAN] Daddy.
[YOUNG JORDAN CRYING]
You're right.
I snapped.
I was reminded of my dad.
You know what happened to Mama.
Back then,
I couldn't protect her from Dad.
But now, things are different.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll do whatever it takes
to protect all of us
from people like my dad.
People like Caloy.
It's just,
I shouldn't have lost control.
I shouldn't have let it go this far.
[BILLY] Mm-hmm.
So, dude, I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
You only did that for…
For us.
- Aww!
- [GIGGLING]
- Kiss her!
- Kiss!
- Uh, it's all settled.
- Hey, Ralph.
Everything's taken care of, Billy.
I called Ralph.
Did you guys forget? His dad is a judge.
- Mm-hmm.
- Ralph, thank you.
Dad took care of it, bro.
He personally called the judge on duty,
so your release was signed right away.
- Thank you.
- Ralph, thank you.
Dude! Hey.
- Thank you!
- [MAN 1] Kiss!
- Come on, just one!
- Just one kiss!
- [JORDAN] You two kiss!
- [MAN 1] Kiss!
[CHEERING]
- Cheers!
- [YANI] Cheers!
- To…
Freedom.
- To freedom!
[JORDAN] To freedom.
- Cheers.
- [BOTTLE CLINKS]
- Ralph.
- Hmm?
Thanks again. You're a real lifesaver.
I got you, brother.
Your boyfriend's family really does have
some serious influence, Charm.
[CHARM] Oh!
That's my Ralph!
- Aw!
- Well, he's a nepo kid.
- [TONI] Hey, come on.
I'm just kidding. Don't be so sensitive!
- To freedom!
- Cheers!
- Freedom, freedom, freedom!
- I'm just kidding!
- He's just kidding.
[BOTTLES CLINKING]
Oh, speaking of freedom,
what about LoveList?
When are we finally going to be free
of that Caloy?
Hmm.
[MARJ] Guys, this is really worrying,
especially now.
Just when LoveLine started bringing
our members back too.
Check your socials.
The haters have multiplied too.
I know.
I'll make a post.
I'll explain everything.
No, no. No need.
The best thing to do is…
No reaction?
Is to think of ways
to improve LoveList's services even more.
And keep promoting our advocacy.
- We can do this.
- Okay.
Cheers. We can do this.
- [YANI] Cheers!
- I'm just going to the restroom.
- [TONI] That's what she said.
- Excuse me.
[CHARM] But seriously, once I find out
who Caloy's accomplice is…
- [CHARM] I swear! I swear!
- [TONI] Yes, girl, stay mad.
- [TONI] Love, come on.
- [YANI] I'm kidding, you guys.
- [YANI] Come on, cheers again!
- [JORDAN CLEARS THROAT]
[FRIENDS] Cheers!
[TONI] You're such a clown.
Go use the restroom already.
All right, that's enough.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hmm?
- Sorry.
No, it's okay.
What's done is done.
There's nothing we can do now.
Let's move on.
You have good intentions.
Are you sure?
At least this time,
you didn't get stabbed.
You only got punched.
[GIGGLING]
Thanks, dude.
Thank you.
But you know what
I've been thinking about?
How did Caloy get there before us?
How did he know you were
going to meet the taxi driver?
I think he'll cooperate.
If not, I'll make him.
What if he's working with Caloy?
This taxi driver
is our best shot right now.
He's our only lead to the woman
who gave him the money.
Whoever she is,
I won't let her ruin LoveList.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You guys are leaving?
I don't want to believe it's Val.
Jordan?
Have you guys seen Jordan?
Jordan!
Hi! Hi!
Are you okay?
Are you okay? What happened?
I'm fine, really.
Tell me everything.
I'm good.
Val.
Beer?
Can you pass it over?
- Pass it over, please.
- Just pass it over.
Thanks.
You know, Jordan,
you really haven't changed.
Guys, back when Jordan and I
were together,
every time someone messed with me,
he'd go after them.
You really need to watch your temper.
But are you okay now?
Did you break any bones?
- When's your next follow-up…
- Val.
I'm okay.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Just let me know.
Is this awkward?
Sorry.
I'm just worried about Jordan.
I mean, I know we're not
together anymore, but
that doesn't mean I should stop
caring about him, right?
I mean, we're friends.
We have history.
- Right?
- Right.
Friends.
Real friends don't snitch.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARJ] And someone tipped Caloy off
about Jordan's plan to
talk to the taxi driver.
So what are you trying to say?
Why don't you just say it to my face?
Well, I think you're the snitch.
- [BILLY] Marj.
- Oh my gosh.
Stop.
We can't just make assumptions, okay?
Chief, I'm sorry.
It's just that if Valerie
really has nothing to hide,
I dare you to show
your messages and calls.
[CHARM] That's right.
So we can finally know the truth, right?
- Exactly.
Hey, let's not do this.
Jordan, what was
the taxi driver's number again?
Let's see if it's in Valerie's phone.
Don't you want to know
if she's involved too?
So I'm still the suspect?
- No.
- [CHARM] You know what?
Just show us your phone
so we can end this, okay?
No!
See? Guilty.
- [MARJ SCOFFS]
- Hey!
- Give me my phone!
- Guys!
- Marj!
- Give it back to me!
- Show it!
- That's enough!
- Give it back! I'll show it!
- Val, just let her.
Come on, let's get this over with.
Just let them.
So you can prove to them that
you had nothing to do with this.
Go ahead.
Them?
[SCOFFS]
Aren't you suspicious of me too?
So what? You're on my side now?
[MARJ] You know, Val,
for the longest time,
Chief Billy was the only one
who kept defending you
when we thought you were involved
with that Caloy guy.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Fine.
No.
What if you delete the evidence first?
- No.
- I'll check it myself.
I'll do it. Give me your password.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
[ABI] Caloy!
- Oh.
- What are you doing here?
Why did you come straight here?
What if someone followed you?
You know, 'Bi…
I'd never put you in danger.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Did Jordan really think…
[CHUCKLES]
he could outsmart me of all people?
Ah, it hurts.
That's because you weren't careful.
Wasn't it you who told me
to scare that driver?
[BILLY] Okay.
How can you be sure
the taxi driver is telling the truth?
I think he'll cooperate.
If not, I'll make him.
What if he's working with Caloy?
Billy, this taxi driver
is our best shot right now.
He's our only lead to the woman
who gave him the money.
Whoever she is,
I won't let her ruin LoveList.
I won't let her do that to us.
To you.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you really okay?
There you go again.
You're making my problems
your responsibility.
- Is it your dad?
- Why do you keep asking me that?
You're like a broken record.
Things can't always be this way.
Not now that I'm finally
getting close to my idol.
- Anything for you, Bea.
- What did you say?!
Okay, give me my phone back.
- What's this?
- Let me explain.
- [SLAMS]
- Oh!
You witch!
Benilda? Sweetie?